【The fate that cannot be liberated】
[해방될 수 없는 운명]
[Episode 21]
[21화]
Regarding destroying the star map,
별지도 파괴에 관해,
I have some ideas.
나에게는 몇 가지 아이디어가 있습니다.
But I still need your Majesty's help .
하지만 아직은 폐하의 도움이 필요해요 .
Speak your mind.
당신의 마음을 말하십시오.
I want to burn down the Star Pavilion.
스타 파빌리온을 불태워버리고 싶어요.
But very crowded.
그러나 매우 혼잡합니다.
So when I act,
그래서 연기할 때
i want your majesty
나는 폐하를 원합니다
Most psychics will leave.
대부분의 심령술사들은 떠날 것입니다.
You want me to find a way
당신은 내가 길을 찾길 원해요
Create a distraction, right?
주의를 산만하게 만드세요, 그렇죠?
Sim.
심.
Whether it's an astrological festival or a ceremony,
점성술 축제든 , 행사든,
I need an hour.
한 시간이 필요해요.
I'll find a way to burn it.
태울 수 있는 방법을 찾아보겠습니다.
It's easy. We have the perfect excuse.
그것은 간단합니다. 우리에게는 완벽한 변명이 있습니다.
Which?
어느?
birthday party.
생일 파티.
I will use prayer as an excuse
나는 기도를 핑계로 삼을 것이다
and summoned all the prophets in the palace.
그리고 왕궁에 있는 모든 선지자들을 불러 모았습니다.
This is not very logical,
이것은 그다지 논리적이지 않습니다.
But I am a willful and rude young emperor.
하지만 나는 고의적이고 무례한 젊은 황제입니다.
No one wanted to say anything.
아무도 아무 말도하고 싶지 않았습니다.
The more one hour,
1시간이 많을수록
I can let them stay out all night.
밤새도록 밖에 있게 해줄 수 있어요 .
[divorce]
[이혼]
Where is your young master?
네 젊은 주인은 어디 있느냐?
The princess is here.
공주님이 여기 있어요.
Master, let’s talk after we see the princess.
주인님, 공주님을 보고 얘기합시다.
Rong Yu, saia.
롱 유, 사이아.
How dare someone like you want me?
당신같은 사람이 어떻게 감히 나를 원해요?
Your Highness.
전하.
Move yourself
스스로 움직여라
The following is.
다음은 다음과 같습니다.
I can't master the kite
나는 연을 마스터할 수 없다
After a few days I couldn't.
며칠 후에는 할 수 없었습니다.
Then I can't perform with you at the Queen Mother's birthday banquet.
그러면 나는 태후의 생신잔치에 당신과 함께 공연 할 수 없습니다 .
I'm shy and not good at conversation.
나는 수줍음이 많고 대화를 잘 하지 못한다.
So I hope you will notify the Ministry of Etiquette.
그러니 예절부에 통보하시길 바랍니다 .
But especially not Mr. Li...
하지만 특히 리씨는 아니죠...
What gives a servant like you a voice?
당신 같은 하인이 목소리를 낼 수 있는 이유는 무엇입니까?
I've crossed a line.
나는 선을 넘었습니다.
say something.
뭔가 말해보세요.
Zhangping
장핑
- Let's go back. - Yes.
- 돌아가자. - 예.
I haven't finished speaking yet. Why are you leaving?
아직 말 안 끝났어요. 왜 떠나는거야?
who do you think You Are?
당신은 누구라고 생각하시나요?
Not even a princess is afraid, let alone a young lady.
젊은 아가씨는 말할 것도 없고 공주조차도 두려워하지 않습니다 .
Your Highness.
전하.
I played with whips long before you .
나는 당신보다 오래 전에 채찍을 가지고 놀았습니다 .
Stop being embarrassed.
당황하지 마세요.
Isn’t He Jiuling?
그는 Jiuling이 아닌가?
I've heard some things about you.
나는 당신에 대해 몇 가지 이야기를 들었습니다.
I must say,
꼭 말해야겠습니다,
I feel sorry for you.
정말 안 됐구나.
I won't quarrel with you because of your husband. You can take it back.
나는 당신의 남편 때문에 당신과 다투지 않을 것입니다 . 다시 가져갈 수 있습니다.
As for what happens next,
다음에 일어날 일에 관해서는,
You can do whatever you want.
당신이 원하는 것은 무엇이든 할 수 있습니다.
Are you going to give up the birthday party?
생일파티를 포기할 건가요 ?
About Rong Yu?
롱 유에 대해서요?
What do you mean by "throw away"?
"버리다"란 무엇을 의미합니까?
Fortunately, I was told that there was something wrong with his brain.
다행히도 그의 뇌에 이상이 있다는 말을 들었습니다 .
He doesn't even remember the music score
그 사람은 악보조차 기억하지 못해요
Still looking forward to me performing with him.
아직도 그와 함께 공연하는 것이 기대됩니다 .
he will introduce himself
그 사람이 자기 소개를 할 거예요
Everyone will know he's fine.
그가 괜찮다는 것은 누구나 알 것이다.
Please go away now.
이제 떠나주세요.
Do you think I want to stay?
내가 머물고 싶어할 것 같나요?
I've already said I won't perform with him.
나는 이미 그 사람과 함께 공연하지 않겠다고 말했습니다.
Solve this problem the way you want.
원하는 방식으로 이 문제를 해결하세요.
I warn you.
경고합니다.
Don't try to use me as a shield.
나를 방패로 삼으려고 하지 마세요.
You know where the exit is.
출구가 어딘지 아시죠?
Get the whip. let's go.
채찍을 가져와. 갑시다.
Are you hurt?
상처받았나요?
I'm fine.
잘 지내요.
Do not say.
말 하지마.
Madam, you should give me some medicine.
부인, 약 좀 주세요.
it's all my fault.
그것은 모두 내 잘못이야.
She looks like a princess,
그녀는 공주처럼 보입니다.
But who would have thought she would be crazy?
하지만 그녀가 미쳤을 거라고 누가 생각이나 했을까요?
What do we do now?
이제 우리는 무엇을 합니까?
we have to inform officials
관계자들에게 알려야 해
Do you want to play the sitar alone, or is it better if we don't go?
시타르를 혼자 연주하시겠습니까, 아니면 우리가 가지 않는 것이 좋을까요?
Of course he will.
물론 그럴 것이다.
If it was confirmed, why didn't he go?
그것이 확인되었다면 왜 가지 않았습니까?
Will the young master perform alone?
젊은 스승이 혼자 공연을 펼칠 것인가?
Didn't you say you wanted to be my music teacher?
내 음악 선생님이 되고 싶다고 하지 않았나요 ?
Before you go, play me one more song.
가기 전에 한 곡 더 들려주세요.
The princess is here.
공주님이 여기 있어요.
Long live the Queen Mother. I'm here to wish you a happy birthday.
여왕 어머니 만세. 나는 당신의 생일을 축하하기 위해 여기에 왔습니다.
Come on, sit here.
자, 여기 앉으세요.
How is the situation in the capital?
수도 상황은 어떤가요?
excellent. I eat well and sleep well.
훌륭한. 나는 잘 먹고 잘 자요.
No old man for me.
나에게는 노인이 없습니다.
my father always bothers me
아버지는 항상 나를 귀찮게 하신다
sometimes,
때때로,
Until I got fat.
살이 찌기 전까지는요.
If this is the case,
만일이 경우라면,
I won't say anything more.
더 이상 말하지 않겠습니다.
Compared with Xilan and Chengan,
Xilan 및 Chengan과 비교하면,
cold as stone,
돌처럼 차갑고,
Chu Chu finally came to her senses.
츄츄가 드디어 정신을 차렸습니다.
But from now on,
하지만 지금부터,
Don't use your identity to bully He Jiuling.
He Jiuling을 괴롭히기 위해 자신의 신분을 사용하지 마십시오 .
Regardless of whether she made a mistake or not,
그 사람이 실수를 했는지 안 했는지에 상관없이
I will always support her.
나는 항상 그녀를 지원할 것입니다.
I only had one conflict with her.
나는 그녀와 단 한 번의 갈등을 겪었습니다.
Your Majesty, how did you get there?
폐하, 거기 어떻게 오셨나요?
Did you really abuse her?
정말 그녀를 학대했나요?
European Union...
유럽 ​​연합...
Her family were spies.
그녀의 가족은 스파이였습니다.
She is a bad person.
그녀는 나쁜 사람입니다.
What happened to the He family is an adult issue.
He 가족에게 일어난 일은 어른들의 문제입니다.
Never say those words again.
다시는 그런 말을 하지 마세요.
I know. I won't bully her anymore.
알아요. 나는 더 이상 그녀를 괴롭히지 않을 것입니다.
E a Rong Yu
E a Rong 유
You should be more tolerant of him in the future.
앞으로는 그 사람을 좀 더 관대하게 대해야 합니다.
Don't conflict with him, okay?
그 사람과 충돌하지 마세요, 알았죠?
I will never see these two people again.
나는 이 두 사람을 다시는 볼 수 없을 것이다.
Why should I care?
내가 왜 관심을 가져야 합니까?
Queen Mother, the time has come. We can start the feast.
여왕님, 때가 왔습니다. 우리는 잔치를 시작할 수 있습니다.
he's good.
그는 좋아.
I heard later
나중에 들었는데
You and Rong Yu come to duet.
당신과 Rong Yu가 듀엣을 하러 왔어요.
I am very anxious.
나는 매우 불안하다.
Rong Yu,
유 롱,
We wish you a long and unlimited life.
길고 무한한 삶을 기원합니다 .
Thanks.
감사해요.
bounty happiness.
풍성한 행복.
Why doesn’t the Queen Mother know yet?
태후는 왜 아직 모르시나요?
I'm not going to dance?
나는 춤을 추지 않을 건가요?
Shouldn't this matter be handled by He Jiuling ?
이 문제는 He Jiuling이 처리 해야 하는 것 아닌가요?
If you call me later
나중에 전화하면
I do not know what to do.
나는 무엇을 해야할지 모르겠습니다.
This would be shameful.
이것은 부끄러운 일입니다.
He Jiuling, she did it on purpose.
He Jiuling, 그녀는 의도적으로 그랬습니다.
Your Highness, should we explain this to the Queen Mother?
전하, 이 일을 태후께 설명드려야 합니까?
I wish you a life as good as Nanshan.
난산처럼 좋은 삶을 살기를 바랍니다 .
great.
엄청난.
Great, sit down.
좋아요, 앉으세요.
She was very happy.
그녀는 매우 행복했습니다.
If I tell her these misfortunes
내가 그녀에게 이 불행을 말하면
Will her mood ever get better?
과연 그녀의 기분은 좋아질까요?
- Thank you, Your Majesty. - also,
- 감사합니다, 폐하. - 또한,
She just gave me a tip
그녀는 방금 나에게 팁을 줬어요
She might suspect that I bullied Rong Yu again.
그녀는 내가 다시 Rong Yu를 괴롭혔다고 의심할지도 모릅니다.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
감사합니다, 폐하.
It doesn't matter. I'm the one who should go
그것은 중요하지 않습니다. 가야 할 사람은 나야
sit down.
앉아.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
감사합니다, 폐하.
Come on, it's our turn to introduce ourselves.
자, 이제 우리 자신을 소개할 차례입니다.
- let's go.
- 갑시다.
You should attend the party.
당신은 파티에 참석해야합니다.
You should too.
당신도 그래야 합니다.
No.
아니요.
tonight,
오늘 밤,
I don't want to own Astrology Pavilion.
나는 Astrology Pavilion을 소유하고 싶지 않습니다 .
I just want to be a free dancer.
나는 단지 프리댄서가 되고 싶을 뿐이다.
[divorce request]
[이혼요청]
Not the future,
미래가 아닌,
Do what you want to do.
네가 원하는 것을해라.
Thank you for taking care of me these past few months.
지난 몇 달간 저를 보살펴주셔서 감사합니다.
met you,
당신을 만났어요,
marry you,
너와 결혼해,
and separate myself from you,
그리고 너와 나 자신을 분리시켜라.
I have no regrets.
나는 아무런 후회가 없다.
You just recovered.
방금 회복되셨어요.
You need to take care of yourself.
당신은 자신을 돌봐야합니다.
Eat well,
잘 먹다,
sleep well,
잘 자다,
And don't do...
그리고 하지마...
Zhanping se preocupa.
Zhanping은 걱정하고 있습니다.
correct.
옳은.
You finally smiled at me
마침내 너는 나에게 미소를 지었다
It's time for you to go back to the party. It's almost time for you to play the sitar.
이제 파티로 돌아갈 시간입니다. 이제 시타르를 연주할 시간이 거의 왔습니다.
careful.
주의 깊은.
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
OK touching.
좋아요 감동.
Great dancer.
훌륭한 댄서.
She is very good.
그녀는 매우 훌륭합니다.
legal.
합법적인.
python.
파이썬.
very good.
매우 좋은.
What a beautiful dance!
정말 아름다운 춤이네요!
I didn't expect there would be a big surprise today.
오늘 큰 서프라이즈가 있을 줄은 몰랐습니다.
Come and reward her.
와서 그녀에게 보상하십시오.
- yes- princess
- 네 - 공주님
Let the princess transform
공주가 변신하자
Then go back and collect your reward.
그런 다음 돌아가서 보상을 받으세요.
So this is the princess.
그래서 이 사람은 공주입니다.
A real sword dance with great charm.
엄청난 매력을 지닌 본격 검무.
The princess will hold her wedding in Xingxiang Pavilion.
공주는 Xingxiang Pavilion에서 결혼식을 올릴 예정입니다.
I think the young master is recovering well.
젊은 스승님은 잘 회복하고 계신 것 같아요.
These two really are a perfect match.
이 둘은 정말 완벽한 조화입니다.
Actually.
실제로.
for me,
나를 위한,
Everyone has amnesia.
모든 사람은 기억상실증을 가지고 있습니다.
Has everyone forgotten Rong Yu's wife?
모두가 용우의 아내를 잊었나요?
It may take me a while to change.
변경하는 데 시간이 좀 걸릴 수 있습니다.
How about rewarding Rong Yu first?
먼저 Rong Yu에게 보상을 드리는 것은 어떨까요?
I see.
알겠어요.
Where is Rong Yu?
유롱은 어디에 있나요?
[divorce paper]
[이혼 서류]
[Astrology Pavilion. 】
[점성술관. ]
quickly.
빠르게.
- quickly. - what happened?
- 빠르게. - 무슨 일이에요?
Madam, the Starry Pavilion is on fire.
부인, 별이 빛나는 파빌리온에 불이 붙었습니다.
Clear green, prepare your horse.
녹색을 맑게 하고 말을 준비하세요.
- Yes - Put out the fire.
- 예 - 불을 끄세요.
Quick, get some water!
빨리, 물 좀 가져와!
Bring water!
물을 가져와!
[Xingxiang Pavilion] Quick, this way.
[싱샹관] 빨리 이쪽으로요.
Fogo!
포고!
Put out the fire quickly.
빨리 불을 끄세요.
Quick, get some water!
빨리, 물 좀 가져와!
Bring water, hurry up.
물 가져오세요, 서둘러요.
As your wife,
당신의 아내로서,
It's not impossible for you to start a fire secretly.
비밀리에 불을 피우는 것이 불가능하지는 않습니다.
But star maps are closely guarded.
그러나 별지도는 철저히 보호됩니다.
Direct incineration is very risky.
직접 소각하는 것은 매우 위험합니다.
And the chances of success are not high.
그리고 성공할 확률도 높지 않습니다.
Better to create chaos.
혼란을 일으키는 것이 좋습니다.
First, set fire to the Astrology Pavilion.
먼저 점성술관에 불을 지르세요.
Disturb this place.
이곳을 방해하세요.
Even if the star chart guards don't come out to put out the fire,
성좌경호원들이 불을 끄러 나오지 않아도
When you show up, they let their guard down.
당신이 나타나면 그들은 경비를 실망시킵니다.
When you arrive at the chart room door,
해도실 문에 도착하면,
[Star Chart Room] sent them to put out the fire.
[별표실]에서 불을 끄기 위해 그들을 보냈습니다.
Come on, here comes the water.
자, 물이 나오네요.
quickly.
빠르게.
What's wrong? How did this happen?
뭐가 문제 야? 어떻게 이런일이 일어 났습니까?
Why are they still standing there?
그들은 왜 아직도 거기 서 있는 걸까요?
We need help. if they don't put out the fire
도움이 필요해. 불을 끄지 않으면
The entire Star Pavilion will be set on fire.
스타 파빌리온 전체 에 불이 붙을 것입니다.
Come. Quickly.
오다. 빠르게.
This way. This way.
이 방법. 이 방법.
The water is coming!
물이 온다!
quickly.
빠르게.
Flatten, quickly.
빨리 펴세요.
It turns out that this is the treasure of Xingxiang Pavilion.
이것이 Xingxiang Pavilion의 보물이라는 것이 밝혀졌습니다.
Rong Yu, I'm sorry.
유롱님, 죄송해요.
quickly.
빠르게.
Come on, water.
자, 물.
star map.
별지도.
The star map is missing.
별지도가 없습니다.
The star map is hopeless.
별지도는 절망적입니다.
- Quickly. - Charts.
- 빠르게. - 차트.
Master.
주인.
too late. stand up.
너무 늦었어. 일어서세요.
This is the salvation bequeathed to us by our ancestors.
이것이 우리 조상들이 우리에게 물려준 구원입니다.
Like a fortune teller, just look at the star chart to find out
점쟁이처럼 별자리표만 봐도 알 수 있어요
This will make our guess more accurate.
이렇게 하면 우리의 추측이 더 정확해질 것입니다.
if it is destroyed,
그것이 파괴된다면,
What can we believe to express the divine order?
신성한 질서를 표현하기 위해 우리는 무엇을 믿을 수 있습니까 ?
The fate of the emperor or the fate of Jialin?
황제의 운명인가 , 아니면 가림의 운명인가?
Even if there is a table,
테이블이 있어도
Divine mission is determined by calculation.
신성한 사명은 계산에 의해 결정됩니다.
It's just an object, not worth grieving.
그것은 단지 하나의 대상일 뿐이며 슬퍼할 가치도 없습니다.
As long as we are here, we have nothing to fear.
우리가 여기 있는 한 우리는 두려워할 것이 없습니다.
Come on, get up.
자, 일어나세요.
Come on, put out the fire.
자, 불을 꺼주세요.
leave.
떠나다.
Are you crazy? By this fire,
제정신이에요? 이번 불로,
Even if you go in, you can't get out.
들어가도 나갈 수가 없습니다.
The map must have been burned.
지도가 불타버린 게 틀림없어요.
Why did you come back again?
왜 다시 돌아왔나요?
Let me go.
가자.
I let it go.
나는 그것을 놔두었다.
Do Not Enter.
입력하지.
Go away.
저리 가요.
It disappears.
그것은 사라진다.
- what happened? - teacher.
- 무슨 일이에요? - 선생님.
Where is the star map?
별 지도는 어디에 있나요?
Fogo.
포고.
fire.
불.
The graphics are missing.
그래픽이 누락되었습니다.
- He disappeared. - teacher.
- 그는 사라졌다. - 선생님.
- The star map is missing.
- 별지도가 없습니다.
star map...
별 지도...
teacher.
선생님.
miss.
놓치다.
♫Drink a glass of blues♫
♫블루스 한 잔을 마셔보세요♫
♫ Love turns to pain ♫
♫ 사랑은 고통으로 변합니다 ♫
♫ Can’t wait for the night♫
♫밤이 너무 기다려진다♫
♫ Flashing lights ♫
♫ 깜박이는 불빛 ♫
♫Drink a cup of vicissitudes♫
♫우여곡절을 한잔 마셔♫
♫I no longer have the impetuousness of my youth♫
♫내게는 더 이상 젊었을 때의 성급함이 없습니다♫
Rong Yu.
유 롱.
At.
에.
teacher.
선생님.
♫ Drink through the highs and lows of your journey♫
♫ 여행의 최고점과 최저점을 모두 마셔보세요♫
miss.
놓치다.
Quickly.
빠르게.
Hold on to me.
나를 붙잡아 라.
♫ A head full of white hair, laughing at troubled dreams ♫
♫ 백발이 가득한 머리, 힘든 꿈을 비웃으며 ♫
♫We spent so many days together and I can’t forget her♫
♫우리는 너무 많은 날을 함께 보냈고 나는 그녀를 잊을 수 없습니다♫
At.
에.
♫ Lament the waste of life♫
♫ 인생의 낭비를 한탄하세요♫
Master.
주인.
At.
에.
♫ Let's drink to remember our sorrow ♫
♫ 우리의 슬픔을 기억하기 위해 술을 마시자 ♫
♫ A head full of white hair, laughing at troubled dreams ♫
♫ 백발이 가득한 머리, 힘든 꿈을 비웃으며 ♫
♫ I can't forget you and all the days we spent together ♫
♫ 나는 당신과 우리가 함께 보낸 모든 날을 잊을 수 없습니다 ♫
What should we do?
우리는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
what can we do?
우리는 무엇을 할 수 있나요?
This is not good at all.
이것은 전혀 좋지 않습니다.
How could this happen?
어떻게 이런 일이 일어날 수 있습니까?
I didn't expect the fire to spread so quickly.
불이 이렇게 빨리 번질 줄은 몰랐습니다 .
I don't have time to leave.
나는 떠날 시간이 없다.
But why is Rong Yu here?
그런데 롱유는 왜 여기에 있는 걸까요?
Wasn't he at the banquet?
그 사람은 연회에 없었나요?
He knows the rules and etiquette well.
그는 규칙과 에티켓을 잘 알고 있습니다.
There was no way he could leave before the party was over.
파티가 끝나기 전에는 떠날 수가 없었다.
Why are there so many people here?
여기 왜 이렇게 사람이 많아요?
Why are there so many people?
왜 이렇게 사람이 많아?
- Missed. - I must be dreaming.
- 놓쳤어요. - 꿈을 꾸고 있는 게 틀림없어요.
This is a dream.
이것은 꿈이다.
Can.
할 수 있다.
He Jiuling, acord.
He Jiuling, 동의합니다.
Wake up.
깨우다.
miss.
놓치다.
Master Rong was only injured.
Master Rong은 부상을 입었습니다.
Moreover, the imperial doctor is also trying his best to treat him.
게다가 황실의사 역시 그를 치료하기 위해 최선을 다하고 있다.
Why?
왜?
You need to take care of yourself.
당신은 자신을 돌봐야합니다.
Chengbi, you talk too much.
청비야, 말이 너무 많아.
Sir Rong, I will retreat first.
롱 선생님, 제가 먼저 물러나겠습니다.
After seeing the chart room on fire
해도 실에 불이 붙은 걸 보고
This lady tried to put out the fire with us.
이 아주머니는 우리와 함께 불을 끄려고 했습니다.
The fire becomes too big to control
불이 너무 커져 제어할 수 없게 됨
So we ran for help.
그래서 우리는 도움을 청하러 달려갔습니다.
Then I lost consciousness after inhaling the smoke.
그러다가 연기를 흡입한 뒤 의식을 잃었습니다.
I don't know what happened next.
다음에 무슨 일이 일어났는지 모르겠습니다.
Little did he know that Madam was trapped in the Room of Stars.
그는 부인이 별의 방에 갇혀 있다는 사실을 거의 알지 못했습니다 .
that's me
그게 나야
Who brought the wolf there.
누가 늑대를 그곳으로 데려왔나요?
go.
가다.
- It can't be. - flatten,
- 그럴 리가 없어. - 평평하게 하다,
- There's no way this lady would do that. - Come on, let's go.
- 이 여자가 그런 짓을 할 리가 없어요. - 자, 가자.
If you take her away, you'll kill her.
그녀를 데려가면 그녀를 죽일 것입니다.
I will leave Rong Yu to you.
나는 Rong Yu를 당신에게 맡길 것입니다.
quickly. go.
빠르게. 가다.
What? He Jiuling, she...
무엇? 그 Jiuling, 그녀는 ...
what did the doctor say?
의사가 뭐라고 했습니까?
He is not in danger.
그는 위험에 처해 있지 않습니다.
But he didn't wake up.
그러나 그는 깨어나지 않았습니다.
This is because
이 때문입니다
He doesn't want it.
그는 그것을 원하지 않습니다.
He doesn't want it?
그는 그것을 원하지 않습니까?
you came today
오늘 왔잖아
Not just to see Rong Yu, right?
단지 Rong Yu를 보기 위해서가 아니죠?
little emperor
작은 황제
Transfer all management rights of the Nagano gold and silver mine to me.
나가노 금은광 의 모든 경영권을 나에게 양도합니다 .
About to leave Nagano.
나가노를 떠나려고 합니다.
Before I leave, I hope you can help me calculate my fate.
떠나기 전에 내 운명을 계산하는 데 도움을 주셨으면 좋겠습니다.
The star map has been destroyed.
별지도가 파괴되었습니다.
After Yu Yu was seriously injured,
유유가 심각한 부상을 입은 후,
astrology center
점성술 센터
Will fall.
떨어질 것이다.
In this case,
이 경우,
I do not want
하고 싶지 않다
Make a guess.
추측해보세요.
Even if I could
내가 할 수 있다고 해도
It would hit my own mark.
그것은 내 자신의 목표에 맞을 것입니다.
I hope your highness can forgive me.
전하께서 저를 용서해 주시기를 바랍니다.
Lord Rong, you are in good health...
롱님, 건강하세요...
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
That disaster was left behind by the He family.
그 재난은 He 가족이 남겨둔 것입니다.
I'll be fine
난 괜찮을거야
Until I saw her die.
그녀가 죽는 걸 보기 전까지는요.
Burn down my astrology studio...
내 점성술 스튜디오를 불태워버려...
How dare she?
그녀는 어떻게 감히?
Why did she suddenly do this?
그녀는 갑자기 왜 이런 짓을 한 걸까요?
it could be...
그것은 수...
I should have noticed something unusual about her.
나는 그녀에게서 뭔가 특이한 점을 발견했어야 했습니다.
she should know
그녀는 알아야 해
Said I was going to destroy the He family.
내가 그 가족을 멸망시키겠다고 말했어요.
You and I are always cautious in our interactions.
당신과 나는 우리의 상호 작용에 항상 신중합니다.
Even the little emperor doesn't know
작은 황제도 몰라요
So how did she find out?
그럼 그녀는 어떻게 알았나요?
What's important now?
지금 중요한 것은 무엇입니까?
the most important is
가장 중요한 것은
It's her who deserves to die.
죽어야 마땅한 사람은 바로 그녀다.
This young man made Yu stupid.
이 청년은 유우를 바보로 만들었다.
And the oldest
그리고 가장 오래된
He broke off the engagement on the pretext of going to Nanjiang .
그는 난장으로 간다는 구실로 약혼을 파기했다 .
There is no good person in the He family.
He 가족에는 좋은 사람이 없습니다.
They must pay the price with their lives for Yu.
유씨를 위해 목숨을 걸고 그 대가를 치러야 한다.
Mr. Rong, I...
롱 씨, 저는...
I made a mistake, that is, I don't have a soft heart.
내가 실수했어요. 즉, 마음이 여린 편이 아니거든요.
My guilt has led to this current disaster.
나의 죄책감이 현재의 재난을 초래했습니다.
when she comes back,
그녀가 돌아오면,
I should ignore Xiaoyu's feelings
샤오위의 감정을 무시해야겠어
Let her and the He family die together.
그녀와 그 가족이 함께 죽게 놔두세요.
Because of this woman,
이 여자 때문에,
At
~에
don't want to wake up
일어나고 싶지 않아
I don’t even want to live anymore.
나는 더 이상 살고 싶지도 않습니다.
very good.
매우 좋은.
very good!
매우 좋은!
she will pay
그녀는 지불할 것이다
A terrible death.
끔찍한 죽음.
I want to see pieces of it.
나는 그것의 일부를 보고 싶다.
i want to burn
불타고 싶어
Her bones turned to ashes.
그녀의 뼈는 재로 변했습니다.
Lord Jung,
정 선생님,
That troublemaker is now gone.
그 문제아는 이제 사라졌습니다.
If we kill her, no one will know.
우리가 그녀를 죽이면 아무도 알 수 없을 거예요.
Don’t worry , before meeting Nagano,
걱정하지 마세요 . 나가노를 만나기 전에
I'll send someone to deal with it
처리할 사람을 보내겠습니다
Avenge King Rong.
복수왕 롱.
Master, some far-sighted people have come to visit you.
스승님, 선견지명이 있는 사람들이 당신을 찾아왔습니다.
teacher.
선생님.
take it easy.
진정하세요.
I should have noticed something unusual about her.
나는 그녀에게서 뭔가 특이한 점을 발견했어야 했습니다.
She must know that I want to destroy the He family.
그녀는 내가 He 가족을 파괴하고 싶어한다는 것을 알아야합니다.
That troublemaker is now gone.
그 문제아는 이제 사라졌습니다.
If we kill her, no one will know.
우리가 그녀를 죽이면 아무도 알 수 없을 거예요.
She will pay a heavy price in death.
그녀는 죽음으로 큰 대가를 치르게 될 것입니다.
Broken, burned.
부서지고 불에 탔습니다.
Master.
주인.
Come on, help me.
어서, 도와주세요.
♫ Dusk as the sun sets♫
♫ 해가 지는 황혼♫
♫I traveled thousands of miles♫
♫나는 수천 마일을 여행했어요♫
♫ Play the sitar under the moonlight ♫
♫ 달빛 아래서 시타르를 연주해 보세요 ♫
♫ Drinks won’t let me forget ♫
♫ 술은 내가 잊지 못하게 해줄 거예요 ♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫내 소망에 관해 당신에게 편지를 씁니다♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있습니다♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 가장 강한 포도주처럼 ♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 운명에는 탈출구가 없습니다 ♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫돌아보면 기다리고 있는 네가 보여♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫ You turn around silently and close the wedding book♫
♫ 당신은 조용히 돌아서서 결혼식 장부를 덮습니다♫
♫Ask how many stars there are in the sky♫
♫하늘에 별이 몇 개 있는지 물어보세요♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫내 소망에 관해 당신에게 편지를 씁니다♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있습니다♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 가장 강한 포도주처럼 ♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 운명에는 탈출구가 없습니다 ♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫돌아보면 기다리고 있는 네가 보여♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫I play the sitar softly waiting for someone like you♫
♫나는 너 같은 사람을 기다리며 조용히 시타르를 연주한다 ♫
♫In the end you are my inevitable destiny♫
♫결국 당신은 나의 피할 수 없는 운명♫